Aden Chan

I am a UXUI Designer based in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. I help companies construct unique visual systems and help enhance the user experience by utilizing less-is-more theory. It help the visual system stand out from its competitors and can also be recognised and remembered by the consumer easily.

adenchan.netlify.app
chunmeng1103@gmail.com
6 018-2749811

Skills

UX/UI Design, Web Develop, Wireframe, Prototype, User Empathy.

Experience

Freelancer • UX/UI Designer

January 2019 - Present

By Utilizing technology and designing tools such as Figma, Adobe Photoshope to create stunning design within a limited timeframe. Received satisfaction from the employer and good feedback from customers.

Astar · Salesperson

January 2018 - January 2019

Push sales and need to hit the target every month. Work as a salesperson has trained my Time Managing skills, Communication skills and Problem-Solving skills. As Good Communication Skills is needed in almost every industry.

Momentum Event · Marketing/Sales Representative

January 2019 - Febuary 2020

In Charge of finding vendors and social media marketing. Dealing with vendor needs and monitor the event tomake sure the event runs smoothly. Raised 20% of new vendors by designing and creating a social media page to make greater exposure compare to traditional text and call method.

Education

Asia Pacific University • Diploma in Information Technology

May 2016 - May 2018

The university provides me with great knowledge and I have learned so many tech-related things around the University such as JAVA, HTML, PHP and getting me ready to start off my career.

Tools

Design • Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop.

Web Development · HTML,CSS,JS,JQuery,Bootstrap.

Wireframe & Prototype · Wireframe.cc, Figma.